本视频由哒哒字幕组原创译制
去死吧
Rot in hell.
给我带来云端之上的眷恋
* Bring me a higher love *
让我悉心体会更高的爱意
* Bring me a higher love, oh, Lord *
主啊  求你用你的话  使我脚步稳当
Lord, direct my footsteps according to your word
《圣经 诗篇》119：133
不许什么罪孽辖制我
and let no sin rule over me.
感谢你保护我的家人
Thank you for protecting my family.
保护我们免受悲剧与疾病的困扰
You've kept us free from tragedy and illness
赐予我们充裕的财富
and you have given us abundance of wealth.
所有的一切
Everything.
只要我一息尚存
As long as I have breath in my body
你的精神存于我心
and your spirit in my heart.
我就是你的仆从与忠实的士兵
I am your servant and your faithful soldier.
阿门
Amen!
让我们看看
Now, let's just see. Oh, yeah.
- 哦  - 看着我的眼睛
- Oh! - Look in my eyes.
让我看看你
Let me see you.
更高的爱究竟在哪里
* Where's that higher love *
每个超级英雄都需要斗篷  妈妈
Well, every superhero needs a cape, Mama.
萝丝  你不要说了  你听到你女儿说的话没有
Oh, Rose, you hush up. You hear your daughter?
好好想想某处是否存在着比肩云端的眷恋
* Think about it there must be higher love *
或许是埋藏于内心深处 又或许宛如遥远的天边繁星
* Down in the heart or hidden in the stars above *
拉近  一号摄像头  取一号摄像头
Push in, camera one. Take camera one.
好了
All right.
你们都在聆听
Y'all are listening today.
不要动  一号摄像头  不要动
Hold steady, camera one. Hold steady.
香港能听到我吗  从挪威到洛杉矶
Can you hear me in Hong Kong? From Norway to LA?
澳大利亚能听到我吗  旧金山湾区
Can you hear me in Australia? The San Francisco Bay.
主的声音在呼唤你  他在翘首等待
The Lord is calling on you now. He's waiting on the line.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
你准备好了  你准备好了吗
Are you ready? Are you ready?
阳光电视台
因为我们时间不多了
'Cause we're running out of time.
我们排练过的台词会在提词器上
Everything we rehearsed will be on the teleprompter.
- 好了  - 埃里克  按台词来
- Okay. - Eric, stick to the line.
去镇住他们  宝贝
Go get 'em, baby.
外面见
I'll see you out there.
- 埃里克  亲爱的  - 快来  儿子
- Eric, honey? - Come on, son.
究竟如何才能寻得
* Try to see falling behind *
看看我们走了多远
Look how far we've come.
25年  多亏了主一切才成为可能
25 years. All things are possible in Him.
- 因为你  - 因为我们
- In you. - In us.
主
Oh, Lord.
偏偏在今天
Oh, it's nice of the Reverend to try and upstage me
牧师跑出来在我自己的电视台跟我抢镜
on my own network on today of all days.
没了你她什么都是不是
He'd be nothing without you.
萝丝  我觉得我们该把翅膀拿出来了
Rose, I think we should get the wings.
给我带来云端之上的眷恋
Be that higher love,
不要走开  25周年特别节目马上开始
and stick around for an extra special 25th anniversary.
就是这样
Yeah, that's right!
向玛格丽特表达你们的爱意
Go on. Show Margaret your love.
愿上帝保佑你们
And may God bless you now.
切
And go.
从美丽的新奥尔良阳光演播室现场直播
Live from Sunshine Studios in beautiful New Orleans.
女士们先生们  玛格丽特·蒙罗
Ladies and gentlemen, Margaret Monreaux!
你们好
Wow! Hello!
乘着翅膀
* On the wings *
你们敢相信吗
Can you believe that?
难以置信
Unbelievable.
你们好
Hello!
快停下  别鼓了
Oh, stop that! No!
这是我的登场  看看他们让我做了什么
I did that! Look what they made me do!
爱你们
Love you!
感谢你们的热情
Thank you for those warm, welcoming words.
我有句话要跟你们说
There is something that I need to say to all of you.
你们和主给了我力量来从事我的事业
You and the Lord give me the strength to do what I do,
感谢你们
so thank you.
我为了戴上翅膀
Now this mama bear has been starving herself for a month
饿了好几个月
to squeeze into those silly wings.
女士们  我觉得我们该来点炸鸡
Ladies, I think it's time we all had some fried chicken.
这就对了
Ah, there you go!
拉斯维加斯 罪恶马车演播室
公鸡跑掉了
Cock on the walk!
那只鸡最好别把我的地毯弄脏
That cock better not mess on my carpet.
咬苹果  宝贝  用力咬
Bite that apple, baby. Yeah, bite it good.
不好意思  堪萨斯城牛肉  你的卡被拒了
Sorry, Kansas City Beef. Your card was declined.
什么  你能再试一下嘛
What? Can you--can you run it again?
- 金杰  - 怎么了
- Ginger. - Yeah.
你最好去看看你妈
You better go check on your mom.
她又在看那个电视节目了
She's watching that TV show again.
我要感谢所有的母亲
Thank you to all my mama bears
25年来的支持
for 25 years of support.
她的台风简直完美
She has the perfect pageant wave.
等我们回来
When we come back,
我有一项令人兴奋的事要宣布
I have an exciting announcement--
我还在看呢  你在做什么
I was watching that. What are you doing?
- 你得停下了  - 不
- You have to stop. - No.
- 你都着魔了  - 没有
- You're obsessed. - No.
都成瘾了
You have a problem.
你们知道  这个国家的许多人说
You know, many in this country say
拥有我们这样价值观的人
that people with our morals
和现实脱节  甚至说我们蠢
are out of touch or even stupid.
我们许多的赞助商说 他们不需要你们的光顾
Many of our sponsors wish that they didn't need your business.
是时候在
The time has come
上帝的光辉之下购物了
to start shopping in God's light,
今天开始的四个月后
so four months from today,
你们将能够从我们这里线上购买从书籍
you'll be able to purchase everything from books,
服装到生活用品的商品
clothing, and groceries online from us.
我们可以向你保证每一位雇员
And we can assure you that every employee,
合作伙伴  还有供应商
associate, and vendor...
都和你持有相同的基督教价值观
Will share your Christian values.
你知道有些线上零售商
Did you know that some online retailers
给他们的顾客提供色情影片吗
offer pornography for their subscribers?
对
Yeah.
在你的购物车漂白剂的旁边
Yeah, so next to the bleach in your cart,
你会发现有醉酒青少年和纵欲男孩的黄片
you got Drunk Teen Girls and Boys Gone Wild.
他们甚至还销售叫做屁股黄油的产品
They even sell a product called Butt Butter.
每件你放入赞美车的商品
For every item that you place in your Praise Cart,
20%的收入将投入我们的信仰
20% of it will go back to our faith.
捐献给在一线为上帝
To charities and organizations on the front lines
传播福音的慈善机构和组织
of God's great commission.
朋友们  为你们献上
My friends, I give you Sunny Club.
阳光俱乐部   阳光俱乐部
Sunny Club, Sunny Club.
阳光俱乐部  阳光俱乐部
- 有什么消息  - 估值高到爆表
- What's the early word? - Valuation's off the charts.
这个项目是个宝贝  尤金
You got a real winner with this, Eugene.
我发誓镜头对你的喜爱都要胜过我了
I swear that camera loves his face even more than I do.
对不起  妈妈
I'm sorry, Mama.
我知道我没按稿子来
I know that wasn't the planned speech.
- 不  - 但是我
- No. - But I--
审慎是通向正直的桥梁
Subtlety is the footbridge to integrity.
阿门
Amen.
真正的正直意味着
True integrity means you're the same in public
表里如一
as you are in private.
吸引蜜蜂要用蜂蜜
You attract bees with honey,
不是屁股黄油
not Butt Butter.
跟我过来一下  埃里克
Walk with me, Eric.
我后悔让埃里克娶了那个人的妹妹
I rue the day that Eric married that man's sister.
他们现在是家里人了  我们必须像对待家人一样对待他们
They are family now. We have to treat him as such.
我确实这么做了
And I do.
这才是我的好老婆
Oh, there's my girl!
你怎么不告诉观众
Why didn't you tell the audience
是我给你设计的服装
I designed your outfit?
自信无言  亲爱的
Confidence is silent, honey.
不安才会引出聒噪
Insecurities, well, they're loud.
屁股里射火花的人还好意思说聒噪
Coming from the woman with sparks shooting out her ass?
宝贝  那不是不安  那是舞台效果
Baby, that's not insecurity. That's show biz.
周一直播的时候妈妈会提到的
Mama will give you credit on air Monday morning.
- 谢谢你  爸爸  - 嗯
- Thank you, Daddy. - Mm-hmm.
不要怂恿她
Don't encourage her.
她就是想要通过阳光俱乐部销售她的服装品牌
She wants Sunny Club to carry that clothing line of hers.
这是她的梦想  玛格丽特
I know, it's her dream, Margaret,
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧
离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏
各大应用商店皆可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
扫描即可下载
我不明白我们为什么不能帮她一把
and I don't know why we can't just set her up.
孩子要什么就给什么
It isn't wise to give children things
- 不是明智之举  - 嗯
- just 'cause they ask for it. - Mm-hmm.
亲爱的  对不起  我得走了
Oh, honey, I'm sorry. I'm gonna have to go.
我今晚要赶去华盛顿特区
I'm hopping the jet for D.C. tonight.
- 现在就要走吗  - 对
- Now? - Yeah.
我还指望着你和我
I was hoping that you and I
今晚能一起度过呢
would have some time together tonight.
每次他父亲来访时他都会跟来
* Preacher's son but when his daddy... *
我回来就补偿你
Just as soon as I get back.
每当他们大人聚集起来聊天的时候
* When they gathered 'round and started talking *
比利就会
* That's when Billy... *
然后他会看着我的眼睛
* Then he'd look into my eyes *
上帝都能感受到我的惊愕
* Lord knows to my surprise *
那个唯一能走入我心中的人
* The only one who could ever reach me *
是牧师的儿子
* Was the son of a preacher man *
还多得是呢
Well, plenty more where that came from,
因为我非常富有
because I am one rich son of a bitch.
- 是他，是他，上帝知道就是他
- * Lord knows he was * - * Ooh yes he was *
我还能清楚的记得
* How well I remember *
我珍惜一切和他在一起的时间
* Taking time to make time *
他告诉我他的一切都属于我
* Telling me that he's all mine *
愿主怜悯罪人
Lord have mercy on this sinner.
他是牧师之子
* Was the son of a preacher man *
富 贵 逼 人
本视频由哒哒字幕组原创译制
死亡夺走了他的肉体
Death takes the body,
上帝带走了他的灵魂
God takes the soul,
尤金·蒙罗
信仰让我们相信我们终会再见
and faith lets us know that we will meet again.
他受人爱戴
He was so loved.
保守派偶像
Memorial services held today
尤金·蒙罗的追悼会在今天举行
for conservative icon Eugene Monreaux.
几周以来的在路易斯安那州沼泽地区的
This comes after weeks of searches
搜索未能寻回他的尸体
in the Louisiana marsh failed to recover his body.
校对：一江春水向西流
举国上下都为这位
And right now the nation mourns the loss
因信仰与原则备受爱戴的人
of the man admired for both his faith
纪念尤金·蒙罗
全美哀悼基督教大亨
全国各界领袖参加追悼仪式
统筹：折木奉太郎
离世而哀悼
and his principles.
与此同时  电视台的门面
Meanwhile the face of the network,
玛格丽特·蒙罗  一个月没有出现在直播中
Margaret Monreaux, hasn't been on air in a month.
蒙罗女士
Mrs. Monreaux!
玛格丽特  你认识和你丈夫在
Margaret, did you know any of the women
一架飞机上的女人吗
on the plane with your husband?
为什么会有人问这种事
Why would somebody ask such a thing?
欢迎来到
光彩夺目的
拉斯维加斯
内华达州
金杰·斯威特
Ginger Sweet?
你被传唤了
You've been served.
昂首挺胸没有什么能将我击倒
* Head up nothing gonna take me down *
我好热
I'm so hot!
蕾切尔
Hey, Rach.
我得离开几天
I have to leave for a few days.
在我回来之前你作主
You're in charge until I get back.
好
Okay!
起飞
* Let go *
古怪一点没什么不对
* Ain't no wrong get a little bit wild *
被欺骗的最糟糕的一部分
The worst thing about being deceived
就是知道你不值得得到真相
is knowing you weren't worth the truth.
你要把他的遗嘱对我保密多久
How long were you gonna keep his will from me?
玛格丽特  我希望你回到节目
Margaret, I wanted you to get back on air first.
好让我继续生活在谎言中
So I could continue living a lie?
撒谎的是尤金  不是你
Eugene was lying, not you.
不  我们在对我们的观众撒谎
No, we were lying to our audience.
我们是一个品牌  他的谎言就是我的谎言
We were one. His lie is my lie.
为了传道我忍辱负重
When I think of all the crap that I put up with
保持家庭团结
to carry on with our mission, keeping this family together,
免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
克制自己的欲望
keeping the lid screwed tight on my honey jar
结果他一直在寻花问柳
while he cheated all along.
你还知道
And you knew.
你不能说你不知情
And you can't say you didn't.
拜托  放我一马吧  玛格丽特
Come on. Give me a break, Margaret.
抱歉我说了这些
I'm sorry I said that.
你应当得到更好他的对待
You deserved better from him.
我也应当对你更好些
And from me.
我知道这些是一夜情
I knew there were one-night stands,
但是我没想到会有私生子
but I never dreamed there was a child.
是复数
Children.
继续读
Keep reading.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
纽约  皇后区
这里有个叫安东尼·里维拉的人吗
There a Antonio Rivera here?
我腰缠万贯
* I been going up Mooda Chainz *
钱多到占场子
* Money got yards, got the range *
看我挥金如土
* Check, watch it go yard on the shakes *
尤金·蒙罗是谁
Who the hell's Eugene Monreaux?
对  主要是商务区
Yeah, it's mostly CBD.
科罗拉多  滨水市
很适合疼痛管理的
It's great for pain management
又没有那么多乱七八糟的焦虑症什么的
without all the wiggy-wag and anxiety.
我回头打给你啊
Oh, I gotta call you back.
* It's been so hard to find you *
* Now is the hour, sweet and sour *
- 杰森·康利吗  - 是
- Jason Conley? - Yeah, sure.
你被传唤了
You've been served.
谢谢啊
Thank you.
那个  要不要喝一杯
Hey, do you want a beer?
- 好的啊  - 好的
- Okay. - Okay, great.
进来吧
Come on in.
妈妈  什么着急事啊
Mama, what's the emergency?
你干嘛在抽烟
Why are you smoking?
干嘛还戴着手套
Why are you wearing that glove?
我才不要把直接上弄得都是尼古丁呢
I'm not messing up my nails with nicotine stains.
我是一位需要抽烟的淑女  但我不是抽烟的人
I'm a lady who needs a smoke. I'm not a smoker.
下楼来  玛格丽特
Come downstairs, Margaret.
行吧
Fine!
你们的父亲  是个好人
Your father, he was a good man,
但不是一个忠诚的丈夫
but not a faithful man.
在这段婚姻之外  他还跟三个不同的女人
He had three children outside this marriage
生过三个不同的孩子
from three different women.
- 什么  - 不是吧
- What? - No.
尤金大部分的股份都会留给
While the majority of Eugene's shares
你们的母亲
will go to your mother,
他规定了  有百分之五
he made a provision that 5% be divided
在孩子里面平分
equally between his children,
现在一共五个孩子了
and, well, there are five of you now.
- 我爸才不是这样呢  - 是的
- That's not my dad. - Yeah, it kind of was.
你爸有时候喝点酒
Your daddy would have a few drinks occasionally
就后悔了
and become remorseful,
一定要我把孩子们都加在遗嘱里
and he called me and insists the kids be included
之后呢  又恢复原样
and then later he would reinstate the original will
又去掉那些私生子了
- with no extramarital children. - Oh, my God.
那看来飞机失事前
It seems the drinky-poo will was in place
翻译：Efroimson
又喝了呗
at the time of the crash.
一家人就是要齐齐整整
"Always together makes a family forever."
- 真的扯淡  - 真是虚伪
- What a load of crap. - What a hypocrite.
翻译：一江春水向西流
你干嘛不阻止他啊
Why didn't you stop this?
我哪知道他还有孩子啊
I never knew about the kids!
他确实坦白在拉斯维加斯嫖娼来着
He did fess up about that whore in Vegas.
翻译：behemoth & 二师姐
我气死了
I was so mad,
我们分居了半年
we slept in separate bedrooms for six months,
只给他手了六次
and he only got handies for six more.
我天  老妈
- Oh, Mama! - Okay, Mom.
这不合法的  他还喝多了
This can't be legal, especially if he was drunk.
我能走到现在的位置
I've dealt with a lot of bastards
是跟很多混蛋打过交道的
to get where I am.
这仨肯定也一样
These three will be no different.
埃里克  托马斯牧师不能知道这件事
Eric, Reverend Thomas mustn't find out
贝基也一样
about this, or Becky.
你让我跟我老婆撒谎吗
You want me to lie to my wife?
- 我又不是爸  - 如果被他们知道了
- I'm not Dad. - If they find out,
就完了
it's over.
那这仨人到底是谁啊
Well, who the hell are these people?
* Somebody gotta *
* Gotta raise a little hell *
路易斯安纳  新奥尔良
* Somebody gotta, gotta raise a little hell *
几层
Which floor?
- 跟你一样 - 我也是
- Same. - That's good.
- 大哥  行不行了 -  好的啊
- Bro, do you mind? - Sure.
- 给你抽  - 不是啊
- Knock yourself out, man. - No, dude.
别在我孩子面前抽啊
Don't smoke that in front of my kid.
我就知道不止我自己
Of course I'm not the only one.
我是金杰
I'm Ginger.
看来咱们都是兄弟姐妹啊
Apparently I'm your sister.
我叫富兰克林·李  内部法律顾问
My name is Franklin Lee, in-house counsel,
麻烦出示一下驾照和信件
and I'll need your letters and your IDs.
你们肯定就是金杰  安东尼奥和杰森了吧
You must be Ginger, Antonio, and, uh, Jason.
这个小可爱是谁啊
Well, who's this little cherub?
我儿子  杰西
This is my son, Jesus.
要是有人
Oh, if only somebody
能把小宝贝的味道
could bottle up the smell
收集起来就好了
of little babies.
要是有人能收集  那也是尤金了
If anybody could have, it would have been Eugene.
好了
Well, all right, then.
这是我的孩子们  萝丝和埃里克
These are my children, Rose and Eric.
萝丝
Rose?
我是家族企业的高级副总裁
I'm the senior VP of operations,
至少事态平息之前都是的
at least until the dust settles,
在我看来
and, uh, you know, from my perspective,
我才不会把我家的公司
there's no way I'm giving a single piece
分给妓女
of my family company to a hooker...
小混混
- Hm? - A hoodlum,
和毒贩子的
and a drug dealer.
信不信我把你牙打掉啊
Yo, I'm gonna knock your teeth in, homie.
这是我的蜂鸟蛋糕
This is my humming bird cake.
早上特意为大家做的
I made it myself this morning especially for y'all.
你拉倒吧
Back up.
我不是妓女
I'm not a hooker.
你不是吗
You're not, huh?
我搜索了罪恶马车
Yeah, I pulled up Sin Wagon on my laptop.
修女  挤奶工  农场姑娘
Nuns, milk maids, farm girls,
在那边做着做可鄙最恶心的事情
doing the most despicable, disgusting things.
你定的还是高级会员啊
So you subscribe to our premium package?
- 杰森  要喝点茶吗  - 不用了
- Jason, you want some tea? - You know what?
我不渴
I'm okay.
你不答应她会一直问你的
Oh, she won't stop asking until you say yes.
- 她就这样  - 那来点吧
- It's what she does. - I'd love some.
萝丝
Rose.
我挺吃惊的
It was, uh, quite a surprise that all of you
你们都包含在尤金的遗嘱里
were in Eugene's will.
我们肯定是要竞争的
One which we are prepared to contest, by the way.
但是为了公平
- There's a--- But in fairness
和敏感度起见
and sensitivity,
我们准备跟大家谈个交易
we are prepared to make an offer.
这个取决于DNA测试结果
Contingent on the results of DNA tests
并且大家要签保密协议
and in signing a non-disclosure agreement,
然后每个人
each of you
会拿到一百万美金
will receive $1 million.
希望大家喜欢我的蛋糕
I hope you enjoy my cake,
不过要先提取一下唾液
after you provide your saliva, of course.
我一直知道尤金是我爸  但我穷的跟啥是的
I grew up dirt poor knowing Eugene Monreaux was my father.
你们能生意做这么大
Y'all built this place
都是因为我替你们保守了我身份的秘密
on the back of a secret I kept for you.
我才不会被一百万就打发了呢
I'm not walking away for a million bucks.
你们的估值可是22亿
You're valued at 2.2 billion.
那你还给我们安排经济舱
And you flew us coach?
我要跟我的兄弟们商量一下
I'm gonna need to talk this over with my brothers
之后再答复你们
and we'll get back to you.
慢慢商量没关系
You take all the time you need,
但是为了公司的财政方面考虑
but for the financial wellbeing
需要大家格外谨慎哈
of the company, your discretion is required.
我们不希望被其他人知道这件事
We wouldn't want anyone finding this out
你们也一样
and nor should you.
好了  暂且这样吧
Well, that's all for now.
请吐口水吧
Please spit.
我从工作中学到
In my line of work,
绝望的人
I've learned that a desperate person
多少钱都愿意给
will pay anything.
感谢您美味的蛋糕  蒙罗太太
Thank you for the lovely cake, Mrs. Monreaux.
不客气的
Oh, you're welcome.
我们是不是要跟他们
Maybe we should have some sort
发展一下关系什么的
of relationship with them.
我感觉如果老爸觉得
I mean, I don't know, if Dad thought
- 需要把他们加进遗嘱  - 别说了萝丝
- putting them in the--- Can it, Rose.
进展的如何啊
How'd that go?
什么进展的如何
How'd what go?
你告诉贝基了
You told Becky.
是啊  她是我老婆啊
She's my wife, Mom.
是啊
Yeah.
我们有更大的鱼要钓呢
We have bigger fish to fry.
公司要分崩离析了
The network is falling apart.
公司的业务
The business of the network
您不用担心  牧师
is none of your concern, Preacher.
你很有才的
You are the talent.
谢谢  富兰克林  你还知道这一点
Well, thank you, Franklin, for acknowledging that.
所以我们这样
So here's the plan.
你得重新上镜
You need to get back on air.
大家看阳光电视台目是为了看咱俩
you and me.
没有你我也跟着损失
Without you, I suffer.
不该有人受连累的
No one should be made to suffer.
你让埃里克当执行总裁
So you make Eric the CEO.
我会依照尤金所愿
I will serve in official advisory capacity
成为官方咨询顾问
just as Eugene wanted,
你就可以继续做你擅长的
and you go back to doing what you do best:
做菜和建议
recipes and advice.
埃里克  我们去吃午饭吧
Eric, should we grab that lunch?
玛格丽特安排的不错啊
Margaret really hooked us up.
是啊
Yeah.
家族元老过世之后
Place has been energized with fresh faces
这地方到处都是新面孔呢
since the patriarch passed.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我是卢克·泰勒  每日先锋报的
Luke Taylor, Daily Edge.
你是记者啊
Reporter?
我妈更喜欢称我为
Well, my mother prefers
调查记者
investigative journalist.
很顺口吧
Rolls off the tongue nice, right?
我能问一下
You mind if I ask what business you had today
你今天去蒙罗无限公司干嘛了吗
at Monreaux Unlimited?
先生  麻烦您离开吧
Sir, I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
这里不允许媒体出现
No press allowed.
打给我
You should call me.
大哥  他们富得流油啊  你傻吗
Dude, they're loaded. What are you talking about?
拿了一百万我就可以全职训练  还可以请人照顾杰西了
I could train full time and have child care for Jesus.
大哥  尤金知道你过得这么惨  都没管你
Man, Eugene knew about you and he let you struggle.
我只知道  上一秒我还穷的叮当响
Look, all I know is one minute I'm broke,
在皇后区挥汗如雨拼死拼活的
sweating my ass off in Queens,
下一秒突然一个白人大姐
and the next minute some white lady
给我吃好吃的蛋糕
is offering me a very delicious piece of cake
还要给我一百万
and a million bucks.
这两样我都很喜欢
I'm good with both those things.
这肯定是你人生中第一次
And I bet this is the first time in your life
得到真正的权力吧
that you've got real power.
不是肌肉或者力量  是权力啊
Not strength or muscle, but power.
- 你还不懂吗  - 别说了
- Don't you see that? - Listen.
我要拿钱的
I'm taking the money.
安东尼奥  我是让你跟他们干啊
Antonio, I'm asking you to fight.
咱们这种人啥时候能成功的
When was the last time people like us came out on top?
啥叫咱们这种人
People like what?
你以后就打算这么教育你儿子吗
Is that what you're gonna teach your son?
DNA测试结果出了吗
What about those DNA tests?
都是符合的  除了杰森的唾液样本被污染了
Positive, except Jason's sample was contaminated.
他重新做了
He's retaking his.
我太为你骄傲了
I am so proud of you.
女士们先生们  我们在美丽的新奥尔良
Live from the Sunshine Studios
阳关摄影棚的录制现场
in beautiful New Orleans, ladies and gentlemen,
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧
离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏
各大应用商店皆可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
扫描即可下载
让我们欢迎  玛格丽特·蒙罗
once again, Margaret Monreaux.
谢谢
Thank you.
感谢大家热情的欢迎
Thank you all so much for that warm welcome home.
一个月前
One month ago,
我失去了我挚爱的丈夫  和最好的朋友
I lost my beloved husband and best friend.
我非常想念他
I miss him greatly, and truthfully,
说实话我都不知道自己还能否撑下去
I didn't know if I could go on.
但我想到了尤金最爱的诗词
Then I thought of one of Eugene's favorite verses.
保持警醒
"Be watchful.
坚持自己的信念
"Stand firm in your faith.
如人一般行动  坚强
Act like men. Be strong."
正是因为尤金
Because of Eugene,
因为你们对我们保有的信念
because of your faith in our mission,
我今天回到这里
I'm back here today...
是因为在我们伟大的土地上  我们还有使命
Because we have work to do in our great country.
我们这样胸怀信仰的人
People like us, people of faith,
时常遭受着严酷的打击
we are under constant attack,
现在比以往更加严峻了
and now more than ever,
我意识到  我们要抓紧家人
I realize we must all stay close to our families
护他们周全
and keep them safe.
这样是尤金所希望的
That's what Eugene would have wanted,
无论是在家里
both at home
还是跟演播室的众多家人们
and right here with the family we have in this room.
一家人就是要齐齐整整
Always together makes a family forever.
家庭是这个世界上最宝贵的东西
And family is the most valuable thing in the world.
所以我们才不能
And that's why we're not walking away
被一百万收买
for a million bucks.
其他的孩子们都拒绝了我们的提议
All of the other kids have refused our offer.
都是金杰搞得
It's Ginger.
但是能怪他们吗
Can you blame them for wanting
想要争取更大的地位和利益
a proper seat at the table?
你是跟她一伙的吧
You sound like you're on her side.
我是跟自己一伙的  玛格丽特
I'm on my side, Margaret.
我很爱你  但是如果公司倒闭
I love you but I got a lot to lose
- 我也会失去很多  - 我知道的
- if this company goes belly up. - I know that.
我在卵石滩有个房子
I got the place in Pebble Beach.
你在苏活区有个跃层
You got the loft in SoHo.
你知道我很在乎我的房产的  玛格丽特
Now, you know I like my real estate, Margaret.
我说了我知道的
I said I know.
我就是提醒你
Just saying,
好好从她的角度考虑一下
taking a moment to look at it from her side, okay?
至少谈判的时候不会很被动
That will keep us from being helpless in the negotiation.
蒙罗家的女孩子唯一被动的时候
The only time a Monreaux girl is helpless
就是指甲坏了的时候
is when her nails are drying.
如果金杰想要得到地位
If Ginger wants a proper seat at the table,
就给她一个咯
let's give her one.
我觉得斯威特小姐会很喜欢
I think a ladies luncheon would be of great benefit
女士午餐会的
to Miss Sweet.
玛格丽特  亲爱的
Oh, Madge, darling,
你气色好好啊
- you just look wonderful. - Oh.
你收到我送的巧克力松糕了吗
Did you get the chocolate éclairs that I sent you?
那是尤金的最爱呢
They were Eugene's favorite.
天啊  这谁啊
Oh, dear. Who is that?
一个熟人  先失陪了
An acquaintance. Excuse me.
好的
Of course.
亲爱的玛格丽特
Margaret, darling.
感谢你邀请我
Thank you for the invitation.
你现在应该觉得自己很蠢
You should feel stupid right now,
反正我不觉得
'cause I certainly don't.
你穿了我爱的颜色呢
Why, you wore my color.
你这么短时间哪里找来的裙子
Where did you get that outfit on such short notice?
- 一个朋友连夜寄过来的 -  我很喜欢啊
- A friend sent it overnight. - I love it.
我也喜欢你穿的
Well, I love what you're wearing.
- 这也是你做的吗  - 不是
- You make that, too? - Uh-huh.
我打算推出一个新系列的衣服
I have a whole line planned,
但是都进展不太顺利呢
but somehow I'm not gaining any traction on it.
失陪了
Excuse me.
下午好女士们
Good afternoon, ladies,
欢迎大家来参加年度女士午餐会
and welcome to our annual ladies luncheon.
今年我们关注的重点
This year our focus is
是本市针对于女孩子们的辅导项目
on the city's mentoring program for girls,
我们更愿意称之为
or as we prefer to call them,
培养未来的商业女性
businesswomen of the future.
公司里最近愁云惨淡
It's been a sad time at the network,
所以请大家原谅我
so although I previously agreed to speak today,
尽管之前我答应了要发表演讲
I hope you'll understand and forgive me
但今天我更想要给大家介绍
if I do not, but in my place,
一位成功的女士
I'd like to introduce a woman with a successful company
她白手起家
that she built from the ground up.
让我们欢迎穿着圈环裙的女士
The lovely lady in that charming hoop skirt,
金杰·斯威特小姐
Miss Ginger Sweet.
上来啊  金杰
Come on up here, Ginger!
大家欢迎金杰
Let's welcome Ginger.
不如你先告诉各位
Why don't you start by telling these young ladies
你是做什么职业的吧
what you do for a living, sweetie.
启发一下大家
Inspire them.
我知道你很为自己自豪的
I know how proud you are of what you do.
看来斯威特小姐有点怯场了
Well, it seems that Miss Sweet has a bit of stage fright.
很正常
We've all been there.
不如先让下一位来讲话吧
Why don't we bring up our next speaker
之后我们再处理
and, uh, we'll get this all sorted out?
过来吧  亲爱的
Come on over here, sweetie.
文明社会没有你的立足之地的
There's no place for you in civil society.
我现在愿意给你两百万
I'm offering you two million now,
我已经很慷慨了
which we feel is quite generous,
因为你不过就是我老公
considering you represent no more than ten minutes
爽了十分钟的产物罢了
of my husband's pleasure.
你拿着钱回家吧
You take the money and go home.
最爱给我儿子做饭吃了
Nothing makes me happier than cooking for my boy.
谢谢你过来
- Thanks for coming over. - Aw. Wow.
我不要糖浆了
No, no, no. None for me.
我和贝基现在不吃糖
Becky and I are off sugar.
这是纯天然未过滤的枫糖
It's 100% pure unfiltered maple.
对你有好处的
It's good for you.
富含镁和锌
It's full of magnesium and zinc and--
好了好了
All right, all right.
你叫我来干嘛
Why am I here?
我仔细想了  也祈祷过了
Well, I've thought about it and I've prayed on it,
我觉得你还没准备好
and I don't think you're ready
接替你爸的位置
to take your father's place in the company.
现在多少双眼睛都看着呢
Now, the world is watching and we need
我们得暂时慢慢来
to take things very slowly for a beat.
干嘛要慢慢来
Slow? No, why slow?
公司需要采取行动
The company needs to take action
立刻为未来做打算啊
to preserve its future now.
儿子  可能这句话你不爱听
Son, this may not feel like a loving statement but...
但你还缺乏打磨
You lack polish.
枫糖也是糖  妈妈
Maple syrup is still sugar, Mama.
你可以随意粉饰
You can dress it up all you like.
但还是致命的
It's still gonna kill you.
老爸跟牧师说过  想要我接替他的
Dad told the Reverend he wanted me to take over.
你为什么要否定我
Why are you denying me?
难道老爸的话不算数吗
What, doesn't Dad get a say in any of this,
还是你已经把他忘记了
or have you already forgotten him?
快去吧  富兰克林  妈妈给大家发糖呢
Come on in, Franklin. Mom's serving up sugar.
咱们的客人们已经让人议论纷纷了
Rumors starting to fly about our hotel guests.
最好是不让大众看到他们吧
Might be best to keep them out of public view.
先把他们带到营地去
We'll bring them out to the camp.
让大家都冷静一下
Let everybody simmer down for a bit.
该把尤金换掉了
It's time to replace Eugene.
为了全家
For the sake of the family.
厄尔
Earl.
给你的  宝贝
This is for you, baby.
埃里克
Eric!
持续来关注
NEWSCASTER: For more on this developing story,
我们跟随镜头一起来到
we take you live to the company's headquarters
新奥尔良的公司总部
- at downtown New Orleans... - You all right?
此时正在召开新闻发布会
NEWSCASTER: Where a news conference is happening now.
我跟观众们以及各位股东们保证
I would like to assure our audience
我们的公司
and our shareholders that we are far
绝不会是群龙无首的状态
from a rudderless ship.
蒙罗无限公司会继续以家族企业的形式发展
Monreaux Unlimited will remain in the family
依旧掌握在负责人可供信赖的人手中
in trusted, responsible hands.
此决议即刻生效
Effective immediately,
蒙罗无限公司的新任执行总裁为
the new CEO for Monreaux Unlimited
玛格丽特·蒙罗
will be Margaret Monreaux.
谢谢
MARGARET: Thank you.
感谢大家
Thank you all so much.
你妈真不要脸
Your mom's a bitch.
我非常看重自己的责任
MARGARET: I take this responsibility seriously.
二百万呢
- Two million? - Wow.
- 漂亮啊  - 我不干
- Well done. - I'm not taking it.
为什么
Why?
不拿就亏了
I can see a loss when it's coming.
我们值得更多的
We're worth more.
我们仨都是  他们是想抹除我们
All of us are worth more. They're trying to erase us.
如果我要被人抹除  也得花大代价
If I'm gonna be erased, it's gonna cost her.
早上好
Good morning.
蒙罗太太邀请大家
Mrs. Monreaux has invited you all
去到打猎营地居住
to stay at her hunting camp.
干嘛  开枪打我们吗
So she can shoot us?
我跟你说
Yo, yo, look.
你乐意待着就待着吧  我要去了
You can stay here if you want, but I'm going.
我也是  我不值更多钱了
Me, too. I'm not worth more.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe my own mother
我亲妈竟然在我眼皮子底下抢我的工作
would take a job from right underneath me!
- 我可是沃顿毕业的  - 你差点退学了
- I went to Wharton! - You about flunked out.
你觉得你执掌大权
You think the Reverend's gonna be reassured
牧师会放心吗
with you at the helm?
你给我说话注意点
You watch that tongue, young man.
电视台是我一手创立的
I created the network,
我的节目收视率也是最高的
I have the most-watched lifestyle show on TV,
而且我是你妈
and I am your mother.
你不可以不尊重我
I will not tolerate disrespect.
埃里克
Hey, Eric.
我们的兄弟姐妹们来了
Our sister and brothers are here.
要跟我们一起住呢
They're staying with us.
你真他么疯了
You have lost your damn mind!
欢迎大家来到营地
Welcome to the camp.
跟自己家一样别客气  把鞋脱了
Make yourselves at home. Take your shoes off.
我这是周二的袜子
Oh, these are my Tuesday socks,
已经穿到周五了  确定要脱鞋吗
and it's Friday. Are you sure?
你说的有道理
You got a point.
我把帽子摘了好了
I'll take my hat off, then.
安东尼奥  我给你找了保姆
Antonio, I got you a babysitter.
上楼选个房间吧  随便哪个都行
Pick a room upstairs. Any room.
随便吗  谢谢啊
Any room? Ah, thank you.
我带你转转吧
Hey, let me show you around.
- 好的  - 来吧
- Okay. - Come on, okay.
这边差不多就是
So, this is our, like, main...
我在午餐会的时候不该那样的
About lunch. What I did was wrong.
我们都是在经历低潮的意志顽强的女人
We're both strong-willed women working through our emotions,
我希望我们能从头来过
and I'd like it if we could start over.
你真以为我傻吧
You really think I'm stupid, don't you?
当然不是了  金杰
No, definitely not, Ginger.
我学会了  永远不要低估
I've learned never to underestimate
尤金的后裔
Eugene's progeny.
选个房间吧  金杰
Pick a room, Ginger.
我今晚给大家
I'm cooking you all
做一道传统的法国大餐
a traditional Cajun dinner tonight.
我知道你对爸爸的印象可能不太好
I know you probably have some hard feelings towards Dad...
但如果你了解他  你可能会喜欢他的
But I think if you'd known him, you would have liked him.
我说不好
- I don't know about that. - Hmm.
他大概是唯一一个
He was, like, the only person
相信我能成功的人了
who believed in what I'm trying to do.
免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
我可以抽大麻吗
You mind if I smoke some weed?
我太紧张了
Just calms the nerves.
你有什么好紧张的
What do you have to be nervous about?
开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
发生这事  换谁都会想抽的
This entire situation would turn anybody into a pot head.
* Never change, yeah, just always the same *
* Whatever ya need *
* And all you gotta do is call *
我竟然亲你了
I can't believe I did that.
我想要开诚布公的跟你们三个道个歉
I'd like to clear the air and apologize to you three
我失态了
for how I've conducted myself
在无数的祈祷和反思之后
After much prayer and reflection,
我决定  给你们每人
I've decided to give each of you 1%
百分之一的公司股份
of the company.
这是尤金所希望的
It is what Eugene wanted.
但我需要大家签署保密协议
All I ask is that you sign NDAs
保护公司的名声
protecting the reputation
以及我们共同的利益
of the company and our interests in it.
百分之一的股份等于是六百万吧
1% comes out to 6 million.
- 谢谢啊  - 不行
- Thank you. - No.
金杰  你有意识到
Uh, Ginger, you do realize that she's being really,
她现在对咱们超级无敌好了吗
really nice to us right now?
谢谢  安东尼奥
Thank you, Antonio.
我个人想说
Personally, I wanna say
我会接受你的提议  拿钱回家
I will take your offer and go home
以后你们任何人都不会再见到我了
and none of you have to see me ever,
我保证
ever again. I totally promise.
因为我们有五个人
Given there are five of us
包括埃里克和萝丝
including Eric and Rose,
我觉得百分之五更好
I think 5% is a better number.
三千万吗
$30 million?
而且就圣经来讲
And biblically speaking,
数字五象征了上帝的恩典
the number five symbolizes God's grace,
慈爱以及对人类的优待
goodness, and favor toward humans.
这个在圣经里提及了318次呢
It's mentioned 318 times in scripture.
十诫包含两套各五条戒律
The ten commandments contain two sets of five commandments.
前五条关乎我们对待上帝的方式
The first five commandments are related to our treatment
以及和他的关系
and relationship with God,
后五条戒律
and the last five commandments
讲的是我们和他人的关系
concern our relationship with others,
就像我  安东尼奥  杰森  埃里克  还有萝丝
like me, Antonio, Jason, Eric, and Rose.
你觉得呢  萝丝
What do you think, Rose?
三千万够让你乖乖闭嘴
Is $30 million enough to ghost this joint
开创自己的时装品牌吗
and start your own fashion house?
够
Yep.
你简直就是个女神
You are a goddess.
彻头彻尾的女神
Just a complete and total goddess.
我要是能像你这样该多好
I wish I was more like you.
其实你挺像我的  只是你不知道
You're more like me than you know.
我看到了真正的你
I see you.
我看到一个姑娘  永远
I see a girl who spent her whole life
把妈妈放在第一位
making sure her mom was okay
然后再考虑自己
before she even thought to have a thought for herself.
说说你妈妈吧  金杰
Tell me about your mom, Ginger.
那我还是继续听你夸我吧
Can you just keep telling me how awesome I am?
没问题
No prob.
你可能以为你父亲不在乎你
Despite what you may think,
但其实他非常在乎
your father cared deeply about you.
你不知道他关注了你的事业发展
You didn't know it, but he followed your business.
他也不想这样  但却情不自禁地
He didn't like it, but he couldn't help
在你身上看到了他自己的影子
but see a bit of himself in you.
这封信是他最近写的
He wrote this letter recently.
说他时日无多了
Said he wasn't getting any younger.
亲爱的金杰
Dear Ginger,
我想告诉你  我每天都会想到你
I want you to know that I've thought of you every day.
我为你骄傲  因为你能毫不畏惧地
I'm proud of who you are because you're not afraid
做自己
to be who you are.
我一直都很爱你
I've always loved you.
没能成为你的好爸爸  我很懊悔
I wish I'd been the father you deserved.
教友们  一起来  拍起手来
Come on, church! Put your hands together!
鼓掌赞美主
Hands together for the Lord!
我在全力坚持
* Trying just to hold on *
而大地在脚下颤抖
* While the ground keeps shaking *
但我绝不会质疑对主的信念
* But I'm never gonna question who I place my faith in *
不
* No *
不不不  因为冉冉升起
* No, no, no 'cause He rose *
对  他冉冉升起
* Yeah He rose *
我好喜欢听他唱歌
I love when he sings.
是啊
Yeah.
对
* Yeah *
因为他冉冉升起
* 'Cause he rose *
鼓掌赞美主  上帝永生
Hands together for the Lord. He's alive forever.
周二的美食节目
For Tuesday's cooking segment,
教观众做油炸火腿芝士罗勒三明治怎么样
how about deep fried ham cheese basil sandwiches?
当人遇到困厄  神灵就进入他的内心
The spirit comes into a man's heart when he is in need,
神灵说  让我来背负
and the Spirit says, "Lay it all unto me."
埃里克兄弟  把心事倾倒出来吧
Brother Eric, unburden your heart.
谢谢您  牧师
Thank you, Reverend.
对  我的心  我的心很沉重
Um, yeah, my heart is, uh--my heart's heavy
为自己和家人而悲伤
and full of grief for myself and my family,
因为我担心我们迷失了方向
uh, for I fear that we've lost our way.
把真话说出来吧
Speak the truth, all right?
- 上帝在聆听  - 把心事倾倒出来  兄弟
- God's listening. - Unburden your heart, brother.
我父亲  尤金
So my father, Eugene,
你们都
um, the man that--
都认识他  都爱戴他
that you all knew and loved...
但不为人知的是
Unbeknownst to us,
他还有三个
he had three--
马太福音26章15节问道
Matthew 26:15 asks,
如果我把主交给你
"What are you willing to give me
你愿意给我什么
if I deliver Him over to you?"
说起给予  现在有很多商家
Now, there are a lot of businesses out there
只知索取
who take far more than they give
不懂回报
when it comes to deliveries.
他们鼓励用钱投票
They say vote with your dollar.
我则提倡用钱祈祷
Well, I say pray with your dollar.
牧师  能跟您说句话吗
Reverend, can I have a word?
大家好
Hello, everybody.
阳光俱乐部是一个网络组织
Now, Sunny Club is an online fellowship...
我知道你想干什么
I see what you're doing.
你会输的  你听见没
You will lose. You hear me?
你让埃里克掌权  不然全世界都会听到真相
You put Eric in charge or the world hears the truth.
你当年在陋室布道
You were preaching inside a double-wide
是我发掘了你  成就了你
when I found you. I created you.
- 我可不怕你  - 也许你应该怕
- You don't scare me. - Well, maybe I should.
你知道我在香港布过道吗  从挪威到洛杉矶
Can you hear me in Hong Kong? From Norway to LA?
还有澳大利亚
Can you hear me in Australia?
旧金山湾
The San Francisco Bay?
今天之后  你可能连在路易斯安那的
You'll be lucky if they can hear you
庐陵布道都不行了
in Luling, Louisiana after this.
你过分了  首席执行官
You're out of your depth, CEO.
没有了我
You get rid of me,
你那些宝贵的阳光俱乐部顾客会跑光的
you lose all your precious Sunny Club customers.
还会有谁来买你的厕纸
Who'll be left to buy your toilet paper
和贺卡呢
and your greeting cards?
你可能沦落到要去卖臀膜
You might even have to sell Butt Butter.
立即注册
Simply sign up...
失陪  我有节目要做
Excuse me. I have a show to do.
- 诺拉  - 即将上市
- Norah! - They're coming soon.
今天讲路加福音8章17节
Today's sermon is Luke 8:17.
一旦接触到光  任何秘密
"For nothing is hidden that will not become evident
都将暴露  埃里克
when come to light." Eric?
我们都有秘密
We all have secrets.
对吗
Don't we?
- 嗨  - 喂  小宝贝
- Hi. - Hey, baby doll.
瑞秋和我正在想你呢
Rachel and I were just thinking about how much we missed you.
- 嗨  - 你在那里好吗
- Hi. - How's it going down there?
说出来你们可能不信
Well, you're not going to believe it,
但我现在住在他们的乡村豪宅里
but I am staying at their house in the country.
太好了
Of course you are.
- 肯定很大  - 喂  我想跟她说话
- I bet it's huge. - Hey, I wanna talk to her.
亲爱的  你什么时候回来
Honey, when are you gonna come back, huh?
蒂娜  给我  让我跟她说
Tina, give it. Let me talk to her.
好了  瑞秋有话想跟你说
All right, Rachel wants to say something to you.
嘿  你没收到我的短信吗
Hey, did you not get my text?
收到了  我只是  没时间
Yeah, I just--I haven't had time to--
大莎莉把希拉和吉迪给偷猎了
Big Sally poached Sheila and Kitty.
我去商场招人
I have been at the mall recruiting
一连招了四天
for, like, four straight days.
什么？嗯  我在听
Hmm? Yeah, I'm listening.
算了  以后再说吧
Okay, let's just talk about it later.
感觉你真的很忙
Obviously, you're busy there.
对不起  小瑞
I'm sorry, Rach.
去吧  没事
Yeah. You're fine.
只是  别告诉妈妈
It's just that -- don't tell Mom--
但是
but...
我有点喜欢上这些人了
I'm starting to like these people.
尤金给我写了封信
Eugene wrote me a letter.
关于我父亲  我有个问题
I have a question about my father.
你好  亲爱的  我刚才没看到你
Hello, honey. I didn't see you there.
我是左撇子
I'm a lefty.
我妈说是尤金遗传的
My mom told me that I got that from Eugene.
是真的吗
Is that true?
你没事吧  亲爱的
Is everything all right, sweetie?
这封信是右撇子写的
A right-handed person wrote this.
尤金对我的感情根本不是这样的  对吗
Eugene didn't feel this way about me, did he?
是你伪造的吗
Did you fake this?
什么样的人才会干出这种事
What kind of person does that?
我
I...
我不知道该说什么
Uh, I don't know what to say.
我不要你的钱
I don't want your money.
也不要你恶心的家人
Or your disgusting family.
你知道吗  也许有一天
You know, maybe someday
你会成为自己想象中的那个好人
you'll be as good as you think you are,
而且  我还想让你知道
and just so you know,
尤金和我母亲不只是露水情缘
Eugene spent more than ten minutes with my mother.
他们在一起整整一年
They were together for a year.
杰森和我准备接受条件
Jason and I are taking the deal.
好啊  去拿他们的钱吧
Fine. Take their money.
趁他们还有钱的时候  赶紧拿吧
Make sure you get it while they still have it.
别坏了我的好事
Don't mess this up for me.
卢克·泰勒  调查记者
主  我好吃力
I am struggling, Lord.
我难以理解你对我的安排
I am struggling to understand your will for me.
为我指引方向吧
Show me the way.
我会跟从
I will follow.
对不起  他从我手里挣脱了
I'm so sorry. He--he got away from me.
门罗小姐  我只想谢谢你
Um, Miss Monreaux, I, uh--I just wanted to say thanks.
为你所做的一切
For everything.
你将改变我儿子的人生
You're gonna change my little boy's life.
你考虑过教育问题了吗
Have you thought about education?
必须赶紧考虑起来
You--you have to get on that right now.
新奥尔良有很多非常好的学校
There are some amazing schools in New Orleans.
你应该跟他母亲商量一下
You should discuss it with his mother.
她跟我们不在一起
She's not really in the picture.
门罗小姐
Miss Monreaux,
我想告诉你  金杰在接触
I wanted you to know that Ginger's been talking
记者
to the press.
你收到我的信息了吗
Did you get my message?
他们准备好拍我了吗
Are they ready for me?
准备好了  全坐满了  但有个麻烦
Yes, full house, but we got a problem.
什么麻烦  我把独家都给了你
What's the issue? I gave you the exclusive.
我们说好了的
We had a deal.
对  但我老板刚跟人谈了不同的条件
Yeah, but my boss just made a different one.
金杰  别去
Ginger, don't go!
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
感谢你们在如此短的时间内赶到
I thank you for coming together on such short notice.
在过去几天中
In the past few days,
我越来越清楚地看到
it has become abundantly clear
我无法独力胜任这份工作
that I cannot do this job alone.
恭喜  首席执行官
Congratulations, CEO.
尤金的离世
Now with the passing of Eugene,
让我们失去了首席执行官  我失去了丈夫
we lost our CEO, I lost my husband,
萝丝和埃里克失去了父亲
and Rose and Eric lost their father.
但我们也有收获
But we have gained as well.
不为人知的是
Unbeknownst to us,
尤金还有三个孩子
Eugene had fathered three other children.
他们今天也来了
And they're here with us today.
上帝看到一切
God, he sees all,
也宽恕一切
and he forgives all.
尤金呀
Eugene.
我们都知道他不是完人
We all know that he had his demons.
我们也不是  因此我原谅他
We all do, and so I forgive him.
还有托马斯牧师  他也原谅他
And Reverend Thomas, he forgives him.
这才是真正的基督精神
Oh, now that's true Christianity.
不可批判他人  以免也被人批判
Judge not lest ye be judged.
牧师就是这么跟我说的
That's what the Reverend told me,
是他陪我们度过了难关
and he got us through this.
谢谢你  保罗
Thank you, Paul.
上帝会决定让谁进入你的生活
God decides who comes into your life,
但最终让谁留下  是由你的本心决定的
but your heart must decide who stays,
所以  在主的指引下
so with the Lord's guidance,
我欢迎安东尼奥·里维拉  杰森·康利
I welcome Antonio Rivera, Jason Conley,
以及金杰·斯维特进入我们的生活
and Ginger Sweet to ours.
喂  杰森  你  你去哪儿啊
Hey, Jason, where--where you going?
这小可爱  怕镜头
He's a camera-shy cutie.
金杰  快上来
Ginger, get on up here.
我知道你可不害羞
I know you're not shy.
你真以为能在
Did you really think you'd have
太岁头上动土吗
the upper hand with the press in my town?
那边是怎么回事啊
What in Heaven's name is that?
那是我母亲
That's my mother.
这里是地狱吗
Is this Hell?
不  是路易斯安那
No, Louisiana.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧
离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏
各大应用商店皆可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
扫描即可下载
本视频由哒哒字幕组原创译制
合作请加QQ:2643527418
金币
* Gold coin *
一摞又一摞
* Stacks on stacks *
让他们写支票
* Make 'em write that check *
我要现金
* I want hard cash *
绿色钞票
* Greenback *
货真价实
* Oh, that's a fact *
我找对了阶级
* I got the right class *
她多重
* Yo, what's her weight *
红宝石  红宝石  阴和阳
* Rubies, rubies, yin and yang *
瑞士的银行里  英镑叠成山
* Pounds on pounds in Swiss banks *
这是我的语言
* That's the language that I speak *
现在我要睡了
* Now I lay me down to sleep *
阿门
* Amen *